<?xml version="1.0"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MDRacing RSS Feed</title><description>The latest news from MDRacing</description><lastBuildDate>22/09/2007 20:40:58 GMT</lastBuildDate><pubDate>22/09/2007 20:40:58 GMT</pubDate><link>http://www.mdracing.co.uk/index.asp</link><item><title>It's Snowing! - Detailing the Coupe</title><description>With all the new Detailing products just begging to be tried out the weather tried it's very best to prevent any fun this weekend but I managed to get some clear weather for a couple of hours so had a bit of a play! Pictures and full write-up  here...</description><link>http://www.mdracing.co.uk/mcoupe_clean3.asp</link><pubDate>13/01/2008 18:44:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Detailing Products</title><description>n an effort to keep the M Coupe in the best possible condition I decided to get some proper detailing products. It didn't take long to realise there is so much more to cleaning acar than a simple bucket and sponge... hell, it turns out that a regular sponge is possibly one of the worst things you can use to wash your car!! Check out what I've gone for  here...</description><link>http://www.mdracing.co.uk/detailing.asp</link><pubDate>05/01/2008 20:42:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BMW Z3 HID Kit Install - How To Guide</title><description>The majority of BMW Z3's come fitted with a set of normal headlights and are often slated for having very poor night time visibility... however all is not lost with the fitting of an aftermarket HID (High Intensity Discharge) Xenon Headlight Kit. They are very simple to fit and I've put together a guide on fitting them  here...</description><link>http://www.mdracing.co.uk/howto10.asp</link><pubDate>03/01/2008 23:55:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BMW Z3 Rocking Seat Fix - How To Guide</title><description>The seats in the BMW Z3 have an inherent design flaw which means that after time the seats start rocking back and forth on their mounts. It's not a massive movement and one that can often be hard to replicate by hand, but when your sat in the seat and come to a stop or pull off there is a slight movement in the seat back and forth. There is a straight forward fix for this niggle and I've written a how to guide complete with links on where to get new bushes  here...</description><link>http://www.mdracing.co.uk/howto9.asp</link><pubDate>01/01/2008 16:14:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Front Speaker Install - Part 3</title><description>With all the wiring in place yesterday it was down to the fun jobs... the sound deadening and wadding! The write-up, pictures and a little movie are  here...</description><link>http://www.mdracing.co.uk/mcoupe_stereo_front.asp</link><pubDate>27/12/2007 19:28:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Front Speaker Install - Part 2</title><description>OK, so not much progress so far and none yesterday as it was Christmas day... but back out to it today with the goal of getting it all done... HA! Never going to happen, though with failing light I've not got all the wiring in place, the speakers fitted and connected and did a quick sound check to ensure things were wired up. Pleased to say it's all working fine :) Today's pictures and write-up are  here...</description><link>http://www.mdracing.co.uk/mcoupe_stereo_front.asp</link><pubDate>26/12/2007 19:38:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Front Speaker Install - Part 1</title><description>So time to get started with the install ofthe front components... and there I was thinking this would be prety straight, what a fool I was! Having not done anything other than remove and refi the headunit it prooved aquite challenging to pull the doorcards off and routing the cables. I thought it would easily be done in a few hours this afternoon but sadly I've not even finished one side yet! Updated pictures and write-up  here...</description><link>http://www.mdracing.co.uk/mcoupe_stereo_front.asp</link><pubDate>24/12/2007 20:16:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Decent Stereo Install for the Coupe</title><description>Time has come to sort out the useless standard system in the M Coupe... I've already swapped out the headunit for a Becker Grand Prix and after taking lots of good advice from the helpful folk on the Talk Audio I've hopfully put together what will be a nice stealth(ish) system. Check out the install progress  here...</description><link>http://www.mdracing.co.uk/mcoupe_stereo_install.asp</link><pubDate>18/12/2007 22:04:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bimmerfest 2007</title><description>I was kindly invited along by a few of the Z3 M Coupe forum members to the BMW Car Club GB's annual show @ Stoneleigh called Bimmerfest. This was a slightly unusually show in that only ~100 cars are invited to display and it's all indoors (ideal for the unpredictable UK weather!). There was an amazing array of BMW models spanning decades, all immaculately presented. Go take a look at the few pictures I took  here...</description><link>http://www.mdracing.co.uk/bimmerfest_2007.asp</link><pubDate>14/10/2007 11:34:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tried a new cleaning method - 2 Buckets!</title><description>Let the Coupe get well dirty the past couple of weeks with a few customer visits (i.e. lots of miles) so when it came time to clean I tried out a new technique (for me at least) with 2 buckets, one of the soapy stuff and one to rinse the mitt... I can totally see why this is a good way of doing things, the colour of the rinse water and the debris in the bottom of the bucket is telling! It was still a "quick and dirty" clean though but some pics of before/after are  here...</description><link>http://www.mdracing.co.uk/mcoupe_clean1.asp</link><pubDate>30/09/2007 10:57:44 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>
